knee_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Rectus Femoris?", "options": ["Anterior inferior iliac spine", "Ischial tuberosity", "Lateral condyle of femur"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Rectus Femoris?", "options": ["Greater trochanter of femur", "Patella and tibial tuberosity", "Medial condyle of tibia"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Rectus Femoris?", "options": ["Flexes leg and extends thigh", "Abducts leg", "Extends leg and flexes thigh"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Rectus Femoris?", "options": ["Sciatic nerve", "Femoral nerve", "Tibial nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Vastus Lateralis?", "options": ["Greater trochanter of femur", "Ischial tuberosity", "Anterior inferior iliac spine"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Vastus Lateralis?", "options": ["Lateral condyle of femur", "Patella and tibial tuberosity", "Medial condyle of tibia"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Vastus Lateralis?", "options": ["Flexes leg", "Extends leg", "Abducts leg"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Vastus Lateralis?", "options": ["Femoral nerve", "Sciatic nerve", "Tibial nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Vastus Medialis?", "options": ["Intertrochanteric line of femur", "Ischial tuberosity", "Anterior inferior iliac spine"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Vastus Medialis?", "options": ["Lateral condyle of femur", "Medial condyle of tibia", "Patella and tibial tuberosity"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Vastus Medialis?", "options": ["Flexes leg", "Extends leg", "Abducts leg"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Vastus Medialis?", "options": ["Femoral nerve", "Sciatic nerve", "Tibial nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Vastus Intermedius?", "options": ["Anterior and lateral surfaces of femur", "Ischial tuberosity", "Greater trochanter of femur"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Vastus Intermedius?", "options": ["Lateral condyle of femur", "Patella and tibial tuberosity", "Medial condyle of tibia"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Vastus Intermedius?", "options": ["Extends leg", "Flexes leg", "Abducts leg"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Vastus Intermedius?", "options": ["Tibial nerve", "Sciatic nerve", "Femoral nerve"], "answer": "c"}
]
